C. McKay Stevenson

220 Sweet Violet Dr. Holly Springs, NC 27540 (269) 217 - 0531 Mckay800@gmail.com

I am a problem solver, a consensus builder, a relentless warrior and incurable strategist. Above all else, I am a compassionate human being who preservers. My education, training and work experience have equipped me with the ability to motivate and lead a team of individuals, simultaneously accomplish multiple tasks, and entrench systems that develop and retain corporate knowledge.

EDUCATION

KINGSLAND UNIVERSITY

Atlanta, GA

Full Stack Developer - 2021

UNIVERSITY of PHOENIX

Phoenix, AZ

M.B.A - 2008

• Honors: cum laude

WESTERN MICHIGAN UNIVERSITY

Kalamazoo, MI

B.B.A - 2004

• Honors: cum laude

ADDITIONAL SKILLS/CERTIFICATES

• Scrum Master – 2018

scrum.org

• JavaScript, Python, CSS, HTML, SQL,

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

BAR LOUIE RESTAURANTS LLC

RALEIGH, NC

General Manager

September 2015 – March 2020

- Oversee general restaurant operations, including but not limited to;
 - ❖ HR recruitment and retention, scheduling, discipline, and record keeping.
 - ✓ Raleigh, NC had the companies' 3rd lowest turnover rate in 2017 & 2018!
 - ❖ Financial responsible for overall performance of the restaurant.
 - ✓ Achieved $\approx 20\%$ total sales increase 3 years in a row
 - ✓ Reduced overall operating expenses 1% during the same three years
 - ❖ Customer Relations responsible for maintaining excellent customer relations
 - ✓ Raleigh, NC was consistently atop the company's CRM metrics

HIBERNIAN EMPLOYEE GROUP

General Manager

Raleigh, NC June 2011 – August 2015

APPLE GOLD GROUP

Regional Manager

Raleigh, NC Jan 2008 – April 2011